One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now, dance!
هيا ارقصوا
Drink!
اشربوا
Eat! Don't be shy!
كلوا ولا تخجلوا
Oh, I feel lighter without flesh to weigh me down.
أشعر أنني أخف وزنًا دون لحم
I mean, I don't have any flesh.
رغم أنّ لا لحم يكسو جسدي
Because I'm just a skeleton.
فأنا مجرد هيكل عظمي
Time to start searching!
سأباشر البحث
A suspicious reinforced door...
...بابٌ فولاذي مثير للريبة
Something smells off here.
أشمّ رائحة الغموض منه
Not that I have a nose.
رغم أنّ لا أنف لي
What are those dolls?
ما هذه الدُمى؟
A poneglyph?!
بونغليف؟
Soba Mask
مقنع السوبا
Hegemony!
بلاد الجبابرة
We've lost the picture!
قُطع البث
Switch to a different camera already!
غيروا إلى كاميرا أخرى بسرعة
Honestly...
بحق
They broke through the last line of defense and are now climbing up the falls!
لقد تجاوزوا خط الدفاع الأخير ويصعدون الشلال الآن
Whaaat?!
ماذا؟
Keep going!
استمروا
The fish are climbing the waterfalls!
هذه الأسماك تصعد الشلال
It's lickety unbelievable.
لا أصدق ما أراه-بيرورين
Dammit! What are you morons doing?!
سحقًا، ماذا تفعلون أيها الحمقى؟
Don't let them set foot on the island!
إياكم أن تطأ أقدامهم الجزيرة
But we have no troops at the top of the falls!
ولكن ليس لدينا قوات متمركزة أعلى الشلال
Plus, the enemy is immensely powerful!
كما أنهم جميعًا أقوياء
We don't have time to mobilize weapons that could take them down!
لا نملك وقتًا لجلب الأسلحة الكافية لهزيمتهم
Don't panic!
لا داعي للذعر
Viceroy Kaido!
كايدو-ساما
Damn Linlin... She even brought her brats with her.
لينلين تلك، لقد أحضرت أطفالها معها أيضًا
Get your shit together, boys!
كونوا مستعدين يا رجال
This'll be an all-out war!
ستنشب حرب شاملة
We don't have to sit here and wait for them.
لا يجدر بنا الجلوس هنا وانتظارهم
Hmph! What's taking them so long to handle a single ship?!
كل هذا الذعر على مجرد سفينة واحدة
Ancient Saur Saur Fruit: Pteranodon
فاكهة الديناصور نوع: تيرانودون (زون عتيق)
I'll deal with it!
سأتولى الأمر
We're near the top!
نكاد نصل إلى القمة
We're almost there!
سنصل أخيرًا إلى بلاد وانو
Here I am, Kaido!
أنا قادمة يا كايدو
What's that?!
ما ذلك الشيء؟
Is that King?!
أذلك كينغ؟
A pteranodon?!
تيرانودون؟
Shoot him down!
أطلقوا عليه
He fled in disgrace!
لقد هرب بكل شفقة
We made it to Wano!
وصلنا إلى بلاد وانو
Now, let's kill Straw Hat!
والآن، لنقتل قبعة القش
He's still here!
لا يزال هنا
No way!
مستحيل
It can't be!
محال
King, you killjoy!
كينغ، أيها اللعين
I won't let you set foot in Wano!
لن أسمح لكم بدخول بلاد وانو
Dammit!
سحقًا
Mama!
ماما
Hurry up, Franosuke!
أسرع يا فرانوسكي
Hey, why do we have to run?!
مهلًا، لماذا نهرب نحن أيضًا؟
They're after Sangoro the soba cook!
إنهم يستهدفون طاهي السوبا سانغورو
But you helped that soba cook take down a member of the Kyoshiro Family!
ولكنك ساعدت طاهي السوبا بهزيمة أحد أفراد عائلة كيوشيرو
Sorry, I couldn't resist!
اعذرني، كنت متحمسًّا
They're linked to Orochi.
اتضح أنّ علاقةً تصلهم بأوروتشي
So they sent members of the Beast Pirates' Soaring Six out for revenge!
لهذا أرسلوا التوبي روبو من قراصنة الوحوش للانتقام
Oh no! The bad guys?! Damn it!
مصيبة، عدو؟ اللعنة
Thank goodness. It's you guys.
هذا مطمئن، إنه أنتما
It's not safe here. This way!
بات المكان خطرًا، لنذهب من هنا
Okay!
مفهوم
This is bad. It doesn't matter what triggered this anymore.
أيًّا كان السبب، فالوضع الراهن سيئ
If any of you get caught and exposed,
إن قُبض على أحدكم واكتشفوا هويته
things will get dicey.
سنكون في وضع صعب
They'll start searching for the rest of your crew!
لأنهم سيباشرون البحث عن بقية الطاقم
Oh, no! Nami and Robin would be in danger!
هذا سيئ، قد نُعرّض حياة نامي-سان وروبين-تشان للخطر
Let's hope they stick to you three!
لنأمل أن يلحقوا ثلاثتكم فقط
But the moment they discover your ties to the Kozuki Clan,
ولكن إن اكتشفوا تعاونكم مع عشيرة الكوزكي
this twenty-year plan for vengeance will be ruined!
فجهودهم للانتقام طوال عشرين سنة ستضيع هباءً منثورًا
In fact...
كلا
even if you get caught and tortured...
حتى لو قبضوا عليكم وعذبوكم
...you mustn't tell them about the samurai or the minks.
يجب ألّا تخبروهم عن الساموراي وعشيرة المينك
Just keep quiet and...
...الزموا الصمت
let them kill you!
ودعوهم يقتلونكم
You're terrible!
أنت مخيف
Luffy wouldn't say something like that!
ما كان لوفي ليقول هذا الكلام
I'm more practical.
أنا أميل للواقعية
It's fine if they don't know it's us, right?
لن يحدث أيًّا مما قلته طالما يجهلون هويتنا، صحيح؟
Well, then...
...إذًا
Why don't we fight with our faces hidden?!
ما رأيكم أن نخفي وجوهنا ونقاتلهم؟
Avoid fighting for now.
يستحسن تجنّب القتال حاليًّا
Stop acting like you're our captain!
من تظن نفسك لتتصرف كقبطاننا؟
If I get caught...
...إن أمسكوا بي
I'll tell them everything just to get away!
فسأعترف بكل شيء لأنجو بحياتي
Screw you!
كفاك عبثًا يا لعين
Then I'll protect you at any cost!
إذًا سأحميك لئلا تفضحنا
Yes!
مرحى
Some friendship!
أأنتم حقًّا رفاق؟
It's a lady!
إنها سيدة
Soba Shop
متجر سوبا
That's not good!
هذا سيئ
Someone's already after us?!
هل وصلوا إلينا؟
Please stop! We have nothing to do with this!
توقف رجاءً، لا علاقة لنا بالأمر
We serve soba, but we have nothing to do with Sangoro the soba cook!
كوننا نبيع السوبا لا يعني معرفتنا بطاهي السوبا سانغورو
How could you destroy our shop?!
كيف لك أن تدمر متجرنا؟
We can't stay in the city without it!
لا يمكننا العيش في العاصمة من دونه
If you wanna blame someone, blame that fool Sangoro.
عليكما إلقاء اللوم على الأحمق المدعو سانغورو
Tell me where I can find more soba shops!
أخبراني بأماكن بقية متاجر السوبا
Or, call out for Sangoro!
أو اطلبا نجدة سانغورو بأعلى صوت
That jackass messed with the Kyoshiro Family!
إنه أحمق اعتدى على عائلة كيوشيرو
If you refuse...
...إن قاومتما
I'll eat you, too!
فسألتهمكما أيضًا
Sangoro!
سانغورو
Hey!
مهلًا
Sangoro, show yourself!
اظهر يا سانغورو
– Sangoro!
سانغورو
Maybe it's no use.
قد لا تنفع استغثاتكم به
If he's a coward, he'll never show himself!
إن كان جبانًا، فلن يأتي أبدًا
Sangoro!
سانغورو
They're playing dirty!
تهدف خطتهم لاستفزازك
Right now, our priority is escaping!
أولويتنا الهرب حاليًّا
There's no way...
...محال
I can do that!
أن أهرب من عواقب أفعالي
Hey, wait, Sanji!
مهلًا يا سانجي
Stop it! We have nothing to do with him!
توقف، لا علاقة لنا به أيضًا
Then, call out for him...
استغيثوا باسمه إذًا
all of you!
جميعكم
Call for Sangoro, the soba cook!
استغيثوا بطاهي السوبا سانغورو
I'm...
...أنا
here!
هنا
Diable Jambe:
ساق الشيطان
Concassé!
سحق
That's him...
إنه هو
He's...
...إنه
Sangoro of the Special Soba!
طاهي الأوهاكو سوبا المميزة سانغورو
So you're the soba cook...
أنت طاهي السوبا المقصود إذًا؟
You showed up. Don't make it any harder on me.
أتيت أخيرًا، تكبدتُ مشقة لاستفزازك
Hey, this is Page One. I found the target on the sixth block of district two!
هنا بيج ون، وجدت الهدف في الشارع السادس من الحي الثاني
Roger! We'll be there as soon as we can.
عُلم، سنوافيك بأسرع ما يمكن
You can't escape now!
لن تلوذ بالفرار الآن
Dinosaur powers, huh?
تملك قدرة ديناصور إذًا؟
You asshole...
أيها اللعين
What are you doing, Sangoro?!
ماذا تفعل يا سانغورو؟
Let it go! We're done for if Drake and Hawkins come!
توقف، إن أتى دريك وهوكينز فسينتهي أمرنا
I know.
أعلم
That said...
...ولكن
this guy has no idea who I am.
إنه يجهل هويتي الحقيقية
No one will find me out, and I won't get hurt!
لذا لن يكتشف أحد هويتي ولن أتأذى
This loser will go down in an instant.
وسأهزم هذا الأحمق بسرعة
Yeah, having more allies is nice...
زيادة عدد حلفائنا سيصب في صالحنا
but reducing the numbers on the other side helps, too.
ولكن تقليل عدد أعدائنا سيفيدنا أيضًا
Stop talking gibberish!
كفاك ثرثرةً بكلام مبهم
Guys, go on ahead!
يا رفاق، اسبقوني
It'll be fine as long as...
لا مانع، صحيح؟
I hide my identity, right?
ما دمتُ سأبقي هويتي مجهولة
The soba cook really showed up?!
هل ظهر طاهي السوبا حقًّا؟
Is he stupid?! Does he wanna die?!
يا لحماقته، أيريد الموت؟
This is the perfect time to transform.
حان الوقت المثالي للتحول
What's that? Is it a can of something?
ما هذه؟ ما الذي تحتويه هذه العبوة؟
Even if wear this, I won't be like the members of Germa!
حتى إن ارتديتها، فهذا لن يجعلني واحدًا من جيرما
I'm just trying it on for size.
أنا فقط أريد تجربتها
He should've abandoned the town.
كان عليه تجاهل أمر البلدة
What's he gonna do?!
ماذا سيفعل سانغورو؟
We're about to fight an emperor.
نحن بصدد مقاتلة أحد الأباطرة
My stubbornness runs the risk of getting in the way of saving someone.
لذا لا يجب أن أكون عنيدًا
But if I swallow my pride, then maybe I can rush to someone's rescue.
إن تخليت عن كبريائي، فربما أنقذ أحدهم
Even more gibberish!
لا تثرثر بكلام مبهم
Especially if this thing powers me up!
لربما هذه العبوة تمدني بقوة أكبر
Here I go!
ها أنا ذا
What are you doing?
ما الذي فعلته؟
You just changed in midair?
هل غيرت ملابسك في الهواء؟
Black Leg...
...الساق السوداء-يا
Oh, he transformed?! How super!
تحول؟ هذا خارق
Cool! How does it work?!
رائع، ما هذه التقنية؟
Wait. I know that costume from somewhere...
مهلًا، رأيت هذا الزيّ في مكانٍ ما
Oh, yeah! But...
...تذكرت، ولكن
how did he get that suit?!
لماذا بحوزته هذه البذلة؟
That's definitely an enemy of Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
لا مجال للشك، إنها بذلة عدو محارب البحر سورا
He's the number three member of the evil army, Germa 66!
العضو الثالث من جيش الشر جيرما 66، ستيلث بلاك
Hey, why do you know so much about it?!
من أين لك كل هذه المعلومات؟
It's only natural! Everyone from the North Blue knows!
هذا بديهي، الأزرق الشمالي بأسره يعرف هذه القصة المصورة
Whatever!
لا أكترث لهذا
Listen! Never call me Germa again! Understood?!
اسمع، إياك أن تناديني بجيرما، أفهمت؟
I was a devoted fan of Sora, Warrior of the Sea!
كنتُ من معجبين البطل سورا الملقب بمحارب البحر
I hated Germa; they were deplorable villains.
كنتُ أكره الأشرار المدعوين جيرما
I hate them, too!
حتى أنا أكرههم
Hey, you!
يا هذا
You're no ordinary soba cook...
يبدو أنك لست مجرد طاهٍ للسوبا
Who are you?!
عرّف بنفسك
I am...
جيرما
Soba Mask
مقنع السوبا
Soba Mask...
مقنع السوبا؟
No... He's definitely Germa.
كلا، إنها بذلة إحدى شخصيات جيرما حتمًا
That's awful! Change your name!
اختيار سيئ، غير اسمك
Please let us name you!
دعنا نختار لك اسمًا أرجوك
Did you say Soba Mask?! Don't mess with me!
مقنع السوبا؟ لا تعبث معي
Where'd he go?
أين ذهب؟
What?!
ماذا؟
He's floating in midair!
إنه يطفو في السماء
How's that possible?!
كيف يُعقل هذا؟
No doubt about it... That's Germa tech, all right.
لا شك في ذلك، هذه تكنولوجيا جيرما العلمية
The devices on their heels allow them to float...
تمنحهم الأجهزة المثبتة في أقدامهم القدرة على الطفو
Yeah, he has to be...
إنه منهم كما توقعت
That's awesome!
هذا رائع
This is child's play!
إنها محض لعبة طفولية
Way to go, Soba Mask!
أحسنت يا مقنع السوبا
Your attacks are so annoying... They piss me off!
هجماتك مزعجة وتثير غيظي
What the hell is this?!
ما هذا؟
Wow!
مذهل
His punch can't get through!
إنها تصد لكمته
The capes worn by Germa 66...
...تعد العباءة في بذلات جيرما 66
can become solid shields...
درعًا صلبًا مضادًّا للهجمات
I know your moves! Your attacks won't work a second time!
حفظت تحركاتك، لن تطالني هجماتك بعد الآن
Oh no!
هذا سيئ
The real Stealth Black would've used a certain something by now...
إن كانت تلك بذلة ستيلث بلاك حقًّا، فسيستخدم تلك القدرة
I won't let you get away now!
لن تفلت هذه المرة
He disappeared?!
اختفى؟
No way!
هذا محال
People can't just vanish! Where is he?! Where'd he go?!
يستحيل أن يختفي، أين هو؟ أين ذهب؟
Get out here!
اظهر
I thought so.
كما توقعت
Whoa! Huh? Where is he?!
يا لقوته! أين هو؟
He's moving too fast to see!
لا يمكنني رؤيته بسبب سرعته
No, that's a special ability of Germa 66's Stealth Black...
كلا، هذه قدرة خاصة لستيلث بلاك من جيرما 66
He became invisible by projecting the background over his body!
يستطيع التخفي عن طريق عرض البيئة المحيطة به على جسده
Even Sora, Warrior of the Sea, had quite a hard time with him...
حتى محارب البحر سورا كان يعاني في مواجهته
Germa scum...!
جيرما الأوغاد
Whose side are you on?!
إلى جانب من أنت؟
You know way too much about this!
أنت تعرف الكثير عنه
I'm from the North Blue; it's a given.
جميع من في الأزرق الشمالي يعرفه
What's with this suit?! Did I disappear?!
ما هذه البذلة؟ هل اختفيت؟
It's just like the Clear-Clear Fruit?!
إنه تشبه قدرة فاكهة الشفافية
It's the devil fruit I've always dreamed of having...
إنها فاكهة الشيطان التي طالما حلمت بالظفر بها
With the Clear-Clear Fruit, I could become invisible.
يمكنني أن أصير خفيًّا بقدرة فاكهة الشفافية
The dream that fell to pieces...
...حلمي الذي فقدت الأمل في تحقيقه
That's right. You stole a dream from me!
هذا صحيح، لقد سرقت أحد أحلامي
I don't remember doing anything like that. You must be mistaken.
لا أذكر أنني فعلت شيئًا لك، لا بدّ أنك مخطئ
But you ate the Clear-Clear Fruit, crushing one of my dreams, got it?!
لذا أنت يا من أكلت فاكهة الشفافية قد سحقت أحد أحلامي
– That's not his fault!
هذا ليس ذنبه
The dream that fell to pieces...
...حلمي الذي فقدت الأمل في تحقيقه
is now possible because of the Germa tech I despised?
تحقق الآن بفضل تكنولوجيا جيرما التي أحتقرها؟
How ironic...
يا لسخرية القدر
But this ability will definitely be useful...
...ولكن هذه القدرة مفيدة فعلًا
I can make use of this in the women's bath...
في حمام النساء
No, no!
كلا
I can use this to protect my friends! What a dilemma!
ستكون مفيدة في حماية رفاقي، يا للخيار الصعب
An invisible man...? Mighty fishy, if you ask me...
رجلٌ خفي؟ يا للغرابة
Just who are you?!
من تكون أيها الوغد؟
This form seems better suited to fighting an opponent that moves around so much.
بهذه الهيئة، سيسهل عليّ قتال شخص يتحرك كثيرًا
At first I was gonna make you suffer,
كنت أنوي تعذيبك
but I guess I'd better just kill you.
لكنني قررت قتلك الآن
Hey, Jaggy!
أيها المسنّن
I bet you still have some dumplings!
أجزم أنك لا تزال تحتفظ ببعض الدانغو
Come on, Jaggy! Don't pretend to be asleep!
أيها المسنّن، لا تتظاهر أنك نائم
I know you can hear me, Jaggy!
أعلم أنك تسمعني أيها المسنّن
This room is quite old and mysterious...
إنها غرفة قديمة وغريبة
This country has been isolated for centuries...
عُزلت هذه البلاد منذ مئات السنين
And the poneglyphs were invented here.
ونُقشت أحجار البونغليف على أرضها
I'm sure there's one here.
واثقة من وجود أحدها هنا
There must be a hidden door somewhere...
لربما يوجد باب خفيّ
Looking for something?
هل تبحثين عن شيء معيّن؟
No way! How did I miss this?!
محال، كيف لم أنتبه؟
Good!
جيد
Good, good, good, good...
جيد، جيد، جيد، جيد
Komurasaki, play that one tune!
كوموراساكي، أريد منك عزف تلك المقطوعة الآن
As you wish...
طلباتك أوامر
Kuri Beach
شاطئ كوري
Otama, let's have a fair fight!
لنخض نزالًا فرديًّا يا أوتاما
I could ask for nothing better, Chopperemon!
هذا المطلوب يا تشوبايمون
Ninpo: Tree Leaf Technique!
فنون النينجا: تقنية الورق
Ninpo...
:فنون النينجا
Zigzag Run!
الركض المتعرج
Take this!
خذ
I have a hard road ahead if I'm gonna be a bewitching kunoichi.
يبدو أنّ أمامي دربًا طويلًا لأصبح أنثى نينجا فاتنة
I managed to dodge everything...
بالكاد تفاديت كل تلك الهجمات
Excellent work, both of you!
بوركت جهودكما
I'm still worried about Big Bro Luffy...
ما زلتُ قلقة على أخي الكبير لوفي
Don't worry! He'll be all right!
سيكون لوفي بخير، لا داعي للقلق
Raizo hasn't reported back either. It's difficult to not be anxious...
ولكن لم يردنا أي خبر من رايزو منذ مدة، هذا مقلق
Master said that no one has ever escaped the prison in Udon...
لم يشهد سجن مقاطعة أودون أي حالة هرب حسبما قال معلمي
I said he'll be fine! Nin-nin!
سيكون بخير كما أخبرتكم
For now, all we can do is train ourselves!
كل ما يمكننا فعله الآن هو التدرب
Ninpo: Tree Climb Technique!
فنون النينجا: تقنية تسلق الشجر
Nin! Nin-nin!
نين، نين-نين
Were I to possess greater strength, I would save him immediately.
لو أنني أتمتع بقوة كافية لذهبت لإنقاذه حالًا
What is that?
ما ذلك الشيء؟
Nin! Nin!
نين-نين
It's curious...
لسببٍ ما، دائمًا ما ترتدي الأخت كوموراساكي هذا القناع عندما تعزف هذه المقطوعة
That's it! That's it! That's the song!
ها هي المقطوعة
I love it!
إنها تطرب مسامعي
It's a mistake to act suspiciously in the presence of ninja.
من الخطأ التصرف بشكل مريب في وجود النينجا حولك
How naive!
يا لسذاجتك
Don't you know what ninja are?
ألا تعرفين النينجا؟
She could be from overseas.
قد تكون من خارج البلاد
Orochi's Oniwabanshu The personal Ninja Squad of the Shogun of Wano
أونيابانشو أوروتشي فرقة النينجا الخاصة بالشوغن
Why, hello there.
يا مرحبًا بكِ
You're quite the troublesome geisha...
إنكِ غيشا مزعجة
I'll give you a chance to explain.
سأمنحك فرصة للتبرير
Fukurokuju Head of the Oniwabanshu
فوكوروكوجو قائد الأونيابانشو
However, you'll only get the one chance.
فرصة واحدة فقط
You okay, Sangoro?!
هل أنت بخير يا سانغورو؟
Those with ancient-type abilities sure are powerful. However...
...كما هو متوقع من فواكه الزون العتيقة، ولكن
it's not enough to beat Stealth Black.
هذا ليس كافيًا لهزيمة ستيلث بلاك
It hurts a bit, but this thing is durable.
تألمت قليلًا، هذه البذلة منيعة
The capital can't take much more, though.
لكن العاصمة لا يمكنها تحمّل المزيد
Hey! Why are we leaving Sangoro behind?!
مهلًا، لماذا نترك سانغورو خلفنا؟
He told us to go on ahead.
أخبرنا أن نسبقه
I mean, he did, but still...!
...صحيح، ولكن
All right, time to deliver his corpse to Boss Kyoshiro.
والآن، سأسلّم جثته إلى الزعيم كيوشيرو
Who the hell was he anyway?
ولكن من كان يا تُرى؟
Others will come after us, and things will get tricky.
سيأتي مزيد من المطاردين ويصبح الوضع مضطربًا أكثر
We should leave the capital for now. Let's head to Ebisu!
لم يعد بوسعنا البقاء في العاصمة، لنذهب إلى بلدة إبيسو
Shooting Star Soba Kick!
ركلة نيزك أوسوبا
What?!
ماذا؟
Tch! He's pretty tough.
إنه صعب المراس
Where are you?!
أين أنت؟
Where did you go?! Show yourself, Soba Mask!
أين ذهبت؟ اظهر نفسك يا مقنع السوبا
Soba Mask, huh?
مقنع السوبا إذًا؟
I should ask Franosuke and Usohachi to redesign this!
سأطلب من فرانوسكي وأوسوهاتشي تعديل تصميم البذلة
What is it?! A person?!
ما ذلك؟ أهو شخص؟
What an enormous person...!
!يا له من شخص ضخم
Still smaller than a giant, though!
يبدو أصغر من أن يكون عملاقًا
Wh-Who do you think is bigger? Kaido or this person?
أ-أتساءل من الأضخم هو أو كايدو؟
Is it a woman?
أهي امرأة؟
No way!
مستحيل
Big Mo–
...بيغ مـ
Big Mom (Charlotte Linlin) Captain of the Big Mom Pirates
(شارلوت لينلين) بيغ مام قبطانة قراصنة بيغ مام
What's the matter?
ما الخطب؟
Don't speak! You'll wake her up!
لا تتحدثي وإلا أيقظتها
We've got to run! It's all over if she wakes up!
لنهرب حالًا، سيُقضى علينا إن استيقظت
No, it's too late! Running won't work if she's followed us here.
لا فائدة، لا جدوى من الهرب طالما تبعتنا إلى هنا
What are you talking about?
عمّ تتحدث؟
Do you know who she is?
هل تعرفها؟
Everyone knows her! She's...
...الجميع يعرفها، إنها
She is the infamous Big Mom?!
أهذه بيغ مام بشحمها ولحمها؟
You're too loud!
لا تصرخ
Who is Big Mom?
من تكون بيغ مام؟
I'll tell you later!
سأخبركِ لاحقًا
I'll finish her off myself!
سأُجهز عليها الآن
That's right! Think of her as Kaido!
صحيح، سأعدّها مثل كايدو
She's the same as Kaido!
إنها مثل كايدو
I-It's too late!
فـ-فات الأوان
Just run for it!
لنهرب
Where...?
...أين
Where... am I?
أين أنا؟
Who...
...من
am I?!
أنا؟